Guide to the New-York Historical Society Geographic Images Collection circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: New York City Views - Queens
  - Subseries IVB: QUEENS - FLAT MATERIAL
    - Long Island City/Newtown/Sunnyside (Folder FF493)
      Perry House, Broadway and Elmhurst, Newtown, photo by Nash, 1906
      First Presbyterian Church of Newtown, photo by Nash, 1906
      46th-Bliss Street IRT Station, Sunnyside, photo by Wayne Geist, 1985
    - Rockaways (Folder FF494)
      Marine Pavilion, Rockaway, L.I., lithograph of Pendleton, New York
      Woodsburgh House, Rockaway, L.I.
      [Bird's Eye View of the Rockaways and Jamaica Bay], lithograph by O.H. Bailey
      Far Rockaway, Long Island, N.Y., (bird's eye view of Rockaway, with inset images of buildings), lithograph by O.H. Bailey, 1902
      Edgemere Railroad Station, photo circa 1890
    - Woodhaven (Folder FF495)
      1 photograph of damage and debris from a tornado that struck Woodhaven in July 1895, photo by Mauri's Photo Studio, Ozone Park.
- Series V: New York City Views - Staten Island
  Series V New York City Views - Staten Island is arranged in an organizational structure by topic of the view. GENERAL views include aerial views (those taken from airplanes or from the top of a tall building) and birds-eye views (generally 19th-century prints).
  - Subseries VA: STATEN ISLAND - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Views
      - Aerial views (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Beach views (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Happy Land Amusement Park, South Beach (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Views of the Harbor, Bay, and Narrows- Prints (Box 1, Folder 4)
        includes mid-19th century engravings and lithographs, including views by W.H. Bartlett.
      - Views of the Harbor, Bay and Narrows- photos (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - General views (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Buildings
      - Buildings-General (Box 1, Folder 7)
        includes hospitals, schools, government buildings, hotels,and warehouses
      - Churches (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Residences-A - E (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Residences-Billopp House,Tottenville (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Residences-F - P (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Residences-Q - Z (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Restoration-Historic Richmond town (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Transportation
      - Transportation (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Subseries VB: STATEN ISLAND - FLAT MATERIAL
    - General Views - Prints (Folder FF496)
      Encampment of Company A - Tompkins Blues - Capt. John Mayher, at Fort Tompkins, Staten Island, Aug. 20th, 1842, lithograph by Thayer and Co., published by James L. Hewitt.
      Richmond Seminary, Staten Island, N.Y., lithograph by F. & S. Palmer, circa 1847-1848
      The Narrows and Part of Staten Island, lithograph by Deroy, after a drawing by Aug. Kollner, 1850
      View of the New York Quarantine, Staten Island, lithograph by Hayward, 1851
      View of the Marine Hospital and Quarantine Grounds, Staten Island, New York, lithograph by Gustav Wenige, printed by Brown and Quinlan, 1854
      View of the Quarantine Grounds and Buildings, Staten Island, lithograph by G. Hayward, 1858 (3 copies)
      Caprera Hotel and Garden, Clifton, Staten Island, photogravure, circa 1890
      Tottenville, Borough of Richmond, New York, G.H. Bailey, 1902 (photoreproduction)
      Tottenville
      Encampment of Company A – Tompkins Blues – Capt. John Mayher, at Fort Tompkins, Aug. 20, 1842
    - General Views - Photographs (Folder FF497)
      The Old Mill, Fresh Kills Meadow, Richmond, circa 1900
      U.S. Coast Guard Station, Staten Island, photograph by Marilyn Schwartz, 1978
      Richmond Iron Mining Company, Staten Island, 2 photographs of workers by F. L. Huff, circa 1880
      New York Bay from Staten Island, panoramic photograph by A. Loeffler, 1897
    - Buildings (Folder FF498)
      Billop House, a.k.a. the Conference House, (2 photographs)
      Britton Cottage, a.k.a Cubberly House
      Comstock, D.A. House, "Rose Bank," New Brighton, 3 views, lithograph by William Endicott and Co., G.M. Root, delineator
      Cortelyou, Aaron Homestead, a.k.a. Lake or Gifford House
      Dongan, Thomas House (colonial governor of New York, later Earl of Limerick)
      Guyon-Clark House, 360 Guyon Avenue, photograph by E. Wenzel
      Kreuzer-Pelton House, 1262 Richmond Terrace
      Lake-Tysen House
      Ward, W.G., "Oneata," 1867
    - Clippings (Folder FF499)
      Clippings from "The Staten Islander" 1901-1905.
- Series VI: American Views (includes New York State)
  Series II. American Views is arranged alphabetically by state. Within states, views of cities are also arranged alphabetically. In the boxed views, if five or more views of a city exist, that city received its own folder. Within each city, additional folders were also created for buildings, etc. with five or more views.
  - Subseries VIA: AMERICAN VIEWS - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Alabama (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alaska-Captain Amundsen and related (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alaska-Cities and buildings (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alaska-Nome (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alaska-Occupational scenes (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - Alaska-Portraits (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alaska-Scenery (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alaska-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
    - Arizona-Desert Scenes (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
    - Arizona-Grand Canyon (Offsite-box 1, Folder 10)
    - Arizona-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 1, Folder 11)
    - Arkansas (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
    - California- A-L (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13)
    - California-Los Angeles (Offsite-box 1, Folder 14)
    - California-M-T (Offsite-box 1, Folder 15)
    - California-Monterey (Offsite-box 1, Folder 16)
    - California-Sacramento (Offsite-box 1, Folder 17)
    - California-San Francisco-General views (excluding photos) (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
    - California-San Francisco-General Views-photographs (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2-4)
    - California-San Francisco-Chinatown (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
    - California-San Francisco-Earthquake and fire (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - California-Yosemite (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - California-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - Colorado-Clear Creek and Cripple Creek (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - Colorado-Colorado Springs (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - Colorado-Creede (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - Colorado-Denver (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - Colorado-Leadville (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
    - Colorado-Manitou Springs/Garden of the Gods (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - Colorado-Pike's Peak (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - Colorado-Railroads (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - Colorado-Scenery (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - Colorado-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut-A-F (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut-Bridgeport (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut-Fairfield (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut-Farmington (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut-G-L (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut-Greenwich (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut-Hartford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut-M-Q (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
    - Connecticut-Middletown (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut-Milford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut-New Haven-General views (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - Connecticut-New Haven-Yale University (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut-New London (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut-New Milford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut-Norwich (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut-R (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
    - Connecticut-S (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17)
    - Connecticut-South Norwalk (Offsite-box 4, Folder 18)
    - Connecticut-South Wilton (Offsite-box 4, Folder 19)
    - Connecticut-Stamford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut-Stratford (Offsite-box 4, Folder 21)
    - Connecticut-T-Z (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut-Wethersfield (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut-Windsor (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
    - Delaware-A-Z (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
    - Delaware-Dover (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
    - Delaware-New Castle (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - Delaware-Wilmington (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia-General views (photos) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia-General views (prints) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia-Buildings (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia-Churches (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-General (Offsite-box 5, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-Library of Congress (Offsite-box 5, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-Smithsonian Institution (Offsite-box 5, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-U.S. Capitol (exterior) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-U.S. Capitol (interior) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-U.S. Patent Office (Offsite-box 5, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-U.S. Post Office (Offsite-box 5, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-Treasury Department (Offsite-box 5, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-White House (photo) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia-Government Buildings-White House (print) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia-Hotels (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia-Monuments and Statues (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia-Museums (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia-Residences (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
    - Florida-A-N (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
    - Florida-DeLand (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
    - Florida-O-W (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
    - Florida-Palm Beach (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
    - Florida-St. Augustine (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
    - Florida-West Palm Beach (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
    - Florida-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
    - Georgia-A-Z (Offsite-box 6, Folder 12)
    - Georgia-Augusta (Offsite-box 6, Folder 13)
    - Georgia-Savannah (photos) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 14)
    - Georgia-Savannah (prints) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 15)
    - Georgia-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hawaii (Offsite-box 6, Folder 17)
    - Idaho (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
    - Illinois-A-Z (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
    - Illinois-Chicago-General (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Fire (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Hotels (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    - Illinois-Chicago-University of Chicago (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Views (Offsite-box 7, Folder 8)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Exposition 1893-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 7, Folder 9-10)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Exposition 1893-Photos by C.D. Arnold (Offsite-box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Illinois-Chicago-Exposition 1893-Photos by C.D. Arnold (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Illinois-Chicago-World's Fair 1933 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
    - Illinois- Chicago-Chicago Historical Society (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
    - Indiana-A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
    - Iowa-A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kansas-A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kentucky A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
    - Louisiana-A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana-Baton Rouge (Offsite-box 8, Folder 10)
    - Louisiana-New Orleans-A-Z (Offsite-box 8, Folder 11)
    - Louisiana-New Orleans-River Views (Offsite-box 8, Folder 13)
    - Louisiana-New Orleans-St. Francisville (Offsite-box 8, Folder 14)
    - Louisiana-New Orleans-St. Louis Cemetery (Offsite-box 8, Folder 12)
    - Maine-A-K (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
    - Maine-Bangor (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
    - Maine-East Port (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
    - Maine-L-Y (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
    - Maine-Mount Desert Island (Offsite-box 9, Folder 5)
    - Maine-Portland (Offsite-box 9, Folder 6)
    - Maine-Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
    - Maryland-A-Z (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
    - Maryland-Annapolis (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
    - Maryland-Baltimore-General (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
    - Maryland-Baltimore-Churches (Offsite-box 9, Folder 11)
    - Maryland-Baltimore-Homewood Estate (Offsite-box 9, Folder 12)
    - Maryland-Baltimore-Monuments (Offsite-box 9, Folder 13)
    - Maryland-Ellicott's Mills (Offsite-box 9, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts-A-B (Offsite-box 9, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts-Amherst (Offsite-box 9, Folder 16)
    - Massachusetts-Arlington (Offsite-box 9, Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-General (Offsite-box 9, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Boston Common and Public Garden (Offsite-box 9, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Buildings-Commercial (Offsite-box 9, Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Buildings-Government-General (Offsite-box 9, Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Buildings-Government-Faneuil Hall (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Buildings-Government-State House (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Churches (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Monuments and Statues (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Mount Auburn Cemetery (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Residences-Hancock House (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Residences-Paul Revere's House (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Residences-General (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts-Boston-Universities (Offsite-box 10, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts-C-F (Offsite-box 10, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts-Cambridge-General (Offsite-box 10, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts-Cambridge-Harvard University (Offsite-box 10, Folder 12)
    - Massachusetts-Cambridge-Longfellow's House (Offsite-box 10, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts-Cambridge-Residences (Offsite-box 10, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts-Cambridge-Washington's Elm (Offsite-box 10, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts-Chicopee (Offsite-box 10, Folder 16)
    - Massachusetts-Concord (Offsite-box 10, Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts-Dedham (Offsite-box 10, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts-Deerfield-General (Offsite-box 10, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts-Deerfield-Residences (Offsite-box 10, Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts-G-L (Offsite-box 10, Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts-Gloucester (Offsite-box 10, Folder 22)
    - Massachusetts-Lexington (Offsite-box 10, Folder 23)
    - Massachusetts-M (Offsite-box 10, Folder 24)
    - Massachusetts-Marlborough (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts-Medford (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts-N (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts-Nantucket (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts-North Woburn (Offsite-box 11, Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts-O-P (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts-Plymouth (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts-Provincetown (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts-Q-S (Offsite-box 11, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts-Salem (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts-South Hadley (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts-Springfield (Offsite-box 11, Folder 12)
    - Massachusetts-Stockbridge (Offsite-box 11, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts-T-Z (Offsite-box 11, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts-Wellesley (Offsite-box 11, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts-Worcester (Offsite-box 11, Folder 16)
    - Michigan-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - Michigan-Ann Arbor (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Michigan-Detroit (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - Minnesota-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota-Minneapolis (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota-St. Paul (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - Mississippi-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
    - Missouri-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
    - Missouri-St. Louis (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
    - Montana-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nebraska-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
    - Nevada-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
    - New Hampshire-A-Z (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
    - New Hampshire-Concord (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
    - New Hampshire-Lake Views (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
    - New Hampshire-Lake Winnipesaukee (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
    - New Hampshire-Portsmouth (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
    - New Hampshire-White Mountains (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)
    - New Jersey-A - C (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey-Allaire (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
    - New Jersey-Barnagat (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey-Bridgeton (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey-Burlington (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    - New Jersey-D - F (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
    - New Jersey-Elizabeth (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
    - New Jersey-Fort Lee (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey-G - J (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey-Greenville (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
    - New Jersey-Hackensack (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
    - New Jersey-Hoboken (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey-Jersey City (Offsite-box 13, Folder 13)
    - New Jersey-K - L (Offsite-box 13, Folder 14)
    - New Jersey-Lakewood (Offsite-box 13, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey-Long Branch (Offsite-box 13, Folder 16)
    - New Jersey-M - O (Offsite-box 13, Folder 17)
    - New Jersey-Middletown (Offsite-box 13, Folder 18)
    - New Jersey-Morristown (General) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 19)
    - New Jersey-Morristown (Washington's Headquarters) (Offsite-box 13, Folder 20)
    - New Jersey-Newark (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey-New Brunswick (General) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    - New Jersey-New Brunswick (Buccleuch Mansion) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey-Oakland (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey-the Oranges (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
    - New Jersey-P - R (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
    - New Jersey-Palisades (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    - New Jersey-Passaic & Passaic Falls (Offsite-box 14, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey-Paterson (Offsite-box 14, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey-Perth Amboy (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
    - New Jersey-Pompton Lakes (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
    - New Jersey-Preakness (Offsite-box 14, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey-Princeton (General) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 13)
    - New Jersey-Princeton (Princeton University) (Offsite-box 14, Folder 14)
    - New Jersey-Rockaway (Offsite-box 14, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey-S - Z (Offsite-box 14, Folder 16)
    - New Jersey-Shrewsbury (Offsite-box 14, Folder 17)
    - New Jersey-Somerville (Offsite-box 14, Folder 18)
    - New Jersey-Springfield (Offsite-box 14, Folder 19)
    - New Jersey-Trenton (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    - New Jersey-Union (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    - New Jersey-Weehawken (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    - New Jersey-Misc. (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    - New Mexico-A-Z (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    - New Mexico-Santa Fe (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - New York-A (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Misc. (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Artotypes by E. Bierstadt (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Hotels, Lodges (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Lake views (Offsite-box 15, Folder 11)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Mount Marcy (Offsite-box 15, Folder 12)
    - New York-Adirondacks-Mount McIntyre (Offsite-box 15, Folder 13)
    - New York-Albany-General (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    - New York-Albany-General (photos) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    - New York-Albany-Photographs by Augustus Pruyn (folder 1 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    - New York-Albany-Photographs by Augustus Pruyn (folder 2 of 2) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    - New York-Albany-Buildings (General) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    - New York-Albany-Buildings (State Capitol) (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - New York-Albany-Residences (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    - New York-Amenia (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    - New York-Auburn (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
    - New York-B (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
    - New York-Beacon (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
    - New York-Bedford (Offsite-box 16, Folder 12)
    - New York-Berlin (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - New York-Buffalo (General) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - New York-Buffalo (Pan American Exposition 1901) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - New York-CA - CD (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - New York-Catskill (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - New York-Catskill Mountains (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - New York-Catskill Mountain House (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - New York-CE - CH (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - New York-Cherry Valley (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - New York-CI - CO (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - New York-Cohoes (Offsite-box 17, Folder 11)
    - New York-Cold Spring (Offsite-box 17, Folder 12)
    - New York-Cold Spring Harbor (Offsite-box 17, Folder 13)
    - New York-Cooperstown (Offsite-box 17, Folder 14)
    - New York-CR - CU (Offsite-box 17, Folder 15)
    - New York-Craryville (Offsite-box 17, Folder 16)
    - New York-Creedmoor (Offsite-box 17, Folder 17)
    - New York-Croton-on-Hudson-Van Cortlandt Ferry House (Offsite-box 17, Folder 18)
    - New York-Croton-on-Hudson-Van Cortlandt Manor House (Offsite-box 17, Folder 19)
    - New York-D (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - New York-Deerfield (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    - New York-Dobbs Ferry (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    - New York-Dover Plains (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    - New York-E (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - New York-Eastchester-general (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - New York-Eastchester-St. Paul's Church (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
    - New York-East Hampton (Offsite-box 18, Folder 8)
    - New York-Ellisburg (Offsite-box 18, Folder 9)
    - New York-Elmsford (Offsite-box 18, Folder 10)
    - New York-Erie Canal (Offsite-box 18, Folder 11)
    - New York-F (Offsite-box 18, Folder 12)
    - New York-Fishkill (Offsite-box 18, Folder 13)
    - New York-Fort A - Z (except Ticonderoga) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 14)
    - New York-Fort Ticonderoga (prints) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 15)
    - New York-Fort Ticonderoga (photos) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 16)
    - New York-Fulton (Offsite-box 18, Folder 17)
    - New York-G (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - New York-Garrison on Hudson (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - New York-Geneva (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - New York-Glen Island (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - New York-Glens Falls (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - New York-Goshen (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - New York-H (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - New York-Hadley (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    - New York-Hartsdale (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - New York-Hastings-on-Hudson (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)
    - New York-Haverstraw-general (Offsite-box 19, Folder 11)
    - New York-Haverstraw -Joshua Hett Smith House - (Washington's Headquarters) (Offsite-box 19, Folder 12)
    - New York-Hempstead-general (Offsite-box 19, Folder 13)
    - New York-Hempstead-St. George's Episcopal Church (Offsite-box 19, Folder 14)
    - New York-Hudson (Offsite-box 19, Folder 15)
    - New York-Hudson River-General views (folder 2 of 3) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - New York-Hudson River-General views (folder 3 of 3) (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - New York-Hudson River-Hudson Highlands (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - New York-Hudson River-Islands -Bannerman's Island (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - New York-Hudson River-Islands-Cruger's Island (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - New York-Hudson River-Mountains-General (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - New York-Hudson River-Mountains-Anthony's Nose (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - New York-Hudson River-Mountains-Breakneck (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)